mcb.com.pk 2019-05-15

# MCB Bank Pakistan | Quick Links | Privacy Policy

We noticed you are using an outdated version of Internet Explorer. Some features may not work correctly. For the full site experience, please update your Internet Explorer to version 9 or above, or install Google Chrome Frame. 

We advise all visitors and clients to read and understand our privacy policy, and to check it periodically for any updates or revisions. If you have any questions about the content of our statement, please feel free to contact us at: [[email protected]](http://info@mcb.com.pk/)

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which MCB Bank Limited gathers, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Website (each, a "User").

###  Privacy

Users' privacy is very important to MCB Bank Limited. The Bank is committed to safeguard the information Users entrust to us.

###  The Information We Collect

MCB Bank Limited may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including, through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. MCB Bank Limited may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Website or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. (A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Website again). While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be ‘associated’ with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Website.

###  How We Use Information

MCB Bank Limited may use personally identifiable information collected through our Website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by the Bank and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with MCB Bank Limited. We may also use information collected through our Website for research regarding the effectiveness of the Website and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of MCB Bank Limited and its partner companies.

###  Disclosure of Information

MCB Bank Limited may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners (If any) who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users, to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected in connection with a sale of our product and services.

###  Maintenance of Information

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.
